Amelia Olenio Collection of American Woolen Company Photographs 6502 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Various Exec. Of American Woolen Co. (Francis White, President), 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Francis W. White and John White., 1952; Black and White photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Stamped on reverse of photo: "St. Linger Studio, 373 Essex Street, Lawrence, Massachusetts." Photo depicts Francis W. White on the left (1893-1957, president of American Woolen Co.) shaking hands with his son, John White on the right. Taken at the Chamber
  - Item 4: Francis W. White at Chamber of Commerce dinner, 1952; Black and White photograph (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Stamped on reverse of photo: "St. Linger Studio, 373 Essex Street, Lawrence, Massachusetts." Photo depicts Francis W. White (1893-1957, president of American Woolen Co.) behind the podium, shaking hands with an unknown man at the Chamber of Commerce dinne
  - Item 5: Francis W. White and Percy Wardwell, American Woolen Company., 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Stamped on reverse of photo: "Photography by Alton Anderson." Photo depicts Francis W. White (1893-1957), president of American Woolen Co., seated behind the desk, and Percy Wardwell, purchasing agent for American Woolen Co. Probably taken in the company'
  - Item 6: Francis W. White and Charles H. Silver, American Woolen Company., 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Stamped on reverse of photo: "Photography by Alton Anderson." Photo depicts Francis W. White (1893-1957), president of American Woolen Co., seated behind the desk, and Charles H. Silver, general sales manager for American Woolen Co. Probably taken in the
  - Item 7: William Muir, American Woolen Company, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Photo depicts William Muir, vice president in charge of the worsted division (1951) and vice president of manufacturing (1952-53) for the American Woolen Company. 12.5 x 15 cm.
  - Item 8: American Woolen Company executives., 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Stamped on reverse of photo: "Photography by Alton Anderson." Photo depicts, left to right: F.S. Connett, treasurer of American Woolen Company; Francis W. White (1893-1957), president of American Woolen Co., and William Muir, vice president of manufacturi
  - Item 9: Francis W. White, at his desk at the American Woolen Company., 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Stamped on reverse of photo: "Photography by Alton Anderson." Photo depicts White, president of the American Woolen Company at his desk, probably in the company's offices in New York City. 20.5 x 25.5 cm.
  - Item 10: William Muir, American Woolen Company., 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Studio portrait of William Muir, vice president of the worsted division (1951) and vice president of manufacturing (1952-53) of the American Woolen Company. Shown from the chest up. 21.5 x 28 cm. Copy A.
  - Item 11: William Muir, American Woolen Company, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Studio portrait of William Muir, vice president of the worsted division (1951) and vice president of manufacturing (1952-53) of the American Woolen Company. Shown from the chest up. Copy B. 21.5 x 27 cm.
  - Item 12: Francis W. White, American Woolen Company, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Portrait of Francis W. White (1893- 1957), president of the American Woolen Company (1950-53), probably taken in his office in New York City. Shown from the chest up. 21 x 27.5 cm.
  - Item 13: Francis W. White, American Woolen Company, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Portrait of Francis W. White (1893- 1957), president of the American Woolen Company (1950-53), probably taken in his office in New York City. Shown from the chest up. Copy B. 21 x 27.5 cm.
  - Item 14: Francis W. White, seated at his desk at the American Woolen Company., 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Image depicts White posed behind his desk, most likely in the company's offices in New York City. 26.5 x 21 cm.
  - Item 15: Executives of the American Woolen Company, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Stamped on reverse of photo: "Photography by Alton Anderson." Photo depicts executives of American Woolen seated at conference table, left to right: George E. McClellan, vice president and comptroller of American Woolen; Charles H. Silver, general sales m